freedownload32.com 2010-11-02

# Privacy Policy of Free Download 32 dot com

## FreeDownload32.com Privacy Policy

FreeDownload32.com is aware of the importance in protecting the privacy of information provided by its users. Information is never collected from our visitors without their prior knowledge and consent. This Privacy Policy summarizes how we handle that information. 

## Information FreeDownload32.com Collects

FreeDownload32.com collects information about its users during their software submissions, contests, and polls. Information provided to us is used for internal purposes and for periodic opt-in newsletters to which users have subscribed. Information is never collected without the users knowledge. FreeDownload32.com will not reveal information provided by its users to any third party without their permission.

For developers who submit their software to our site, FreeDownload32.com only collects the software author's email address for internal purposes only. Software developers will occasionally receive email regarding their program listings and information regarding site updates which may directly effect the software developer's listing.

## How We Use Your Information

FreeDownload32.com uses the information that we collect from you to process your requests and to inform you of our new service offerings and website updates. Users will not receive e-mail from other companies or individuals unless users have requested to be placed on a list to receive information from our advertisers and/or marketing partners on subjects of interest.

Please be aware that when you click on any advertising banners appearing on our web site that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the their privacy policies and not ours. While we support the protection of privacy on our site, we cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement prior to providing any personal information to and/or interacting with any other web site.

Software developers who hold individual accounts with FreeDownload32.com for the purpose of publishing their software product on our site should be aware that all information provided to us regarding your software products will be used soley at our discretion. FreeDownload32.com maintains the right to add product information, edit product information, or completely remove product information at any time without the consent of the software developer. FreeDownload32.com may also evaluate the product and express its evaluation publicly on our web site. Additionally, visitors to our web site may also rate and review the software developer's product and have that information published on our web site without prior consent from the software developer.

## How to Access, Correct, or Remove Your Information

Users may add, delete, or modify their product information without prior permission from FreeDownload32.com, but before information is published on our site, all product information will be reviewed and must be approved by us. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.

\-- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
\-- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\-- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us by using the [contact form](http://www.freedownload32.com/contact/).
